What's up guys? Today we're going to be
making a Nutella and M&M cookie pie. Add
softened butter and light brown sugar to
a bowl and cream these together. Add one
egg and vanilla and mix these in. Add
flour and bicarbonate of soda and mix to
form a dough. Then add your chocolate
chips and M&M's and fold these in.
Create a lid with a third of the dough
then press the rest into your cake tin
creating a lip around the edge. Fill up
your Nutella into the middle and smooth
it out evenly then place your lid on the
top and press it down to seal the edges.
Bake in the oven then let it cool. Pipe
some Nutella over the top then finish
with a sprinkling of M&M's. Enjoy.